let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which of the following formulas can be used to generate random integers between 1 and 10?",
    answer: "A. 1 + rand() % (10 - 1 + 1)",
    options: [
      "A. 1 + rand() % (10 - 1 + 1)",
      "B. 1 + (10 - 1 + 1) % rand()",
      "C. 10 + rand() % (10 - 1 + 1)",
      "D. 10 + rand() % (10 + 1)"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Format flags may be combined using the _____",
    answer: "A. bitwise OR operator (|)",
    options: [
      "A. bitwise OR operator (|)",
      "B. logical OR operator (||)",
      "C. bitwise AND operator (&)",
      "D. logical AND operator (&&)"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of the following will store the number 320000 as a Float number?",
    answer: "A. counPop = (float) 3.2e5;",
    options: [
      "A. counPop = (float) 3.2e5;",
      "B. counPop = (float) 3.2e6;",
      "C. counPop = (float) .32e5;",
      "D. counPop = (float) .32e7;"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "The arguments that determine the state of the cout object are called",
    answer: "C. format flags or state flags",
    options: [
      "A. classes",
      "B. manipulators",
      "C. format flags or state flags",
      "D. state controllers"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "The following statement where T is true and F is false T&&T||F&&T",
    answer: "A. is true",
    options: [
      "A. is true",
      "B. is false",
      "C. is wrong",
      "D. not applicable in C language"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which of the following statements declares a variable that can contain a decimal number?",
    answer: "C. float payRate",
    options: [
      "A. dec payRate;",
      "B. dec hourlyPay",
      "C. float payRate",
      "D. float hourlyPay;"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "The statement int num[2][3]={ {1,2}, {3,4}, {5, 6} };",
    answer: "B. assigns a value 4 to num[1][2]",
    options: [
      "A. assigns a value 2 to num[1][2]",
      "B. assigns a value 4 to num[1][2]",
      "C. gives an error message",
      "D. assigns a value 3 to num[1][2]"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "A program will have one function prototype for each function defined in the programmer-defined section of the program. (Assume that the programmer-defined section is located below the main function.)",
    answer: "B. false",
    options: [
      "A. true",
      "B. false"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "The standard input stream, which refers to the keyboard, is called",
    answer: "A. cin",
    options: [
      "A. cin",
      "B. cout",
      "C. stin",
      "D. stout"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Elements in an array are identified by a unique _____",
    answer: "C. subscript",
    options: [
      "A. data type",
      "B. order",
      "C. subscript",
      "D. symbol"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "The statement fwrite((char*)&objl, sizeof(objl));",
    answer: "B. writes the data in objl to fl",
    options: [
      "A. writes the member functions of objl to fl",
      "B. writes the data in objl to fl",
      "C. writes the member functions and the data of obj1 to fl",
      "D. writes the address of objl to fl"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "The body of a C++ function is surrounded by _____",
    answer: "C. curly brackets",
    options: [
      "A. parentheses",
      "B. angle brackets",
      "C. curly brackets",
      "D. square brackets"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "Which of the following type casts will convert an Integer variable named amount to a Double type?",
    answer: "A. (double) amount",
    options: [
      "A. (double) amount",
      "B. (int to double) amount",
      "C. int to double(amount)",
      "D. int (amount) to double"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "The loosest type of coupling is",
    answer: "C. external coupling",
    options: [
      "A. data coupling",
      "B. control coupling",
      "C. external coupling",
      "D. pathological coupling"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "Which of the following is a string literal constant?",
    answer: "D. All of the above",
    options: [
      "A. 'Visual C++'",
      "B. '137.45'",
      "C. 'A'",
      "D. All of the above"
    
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 16,
    question: "Which of the following, if any, are valid names for variables?",
    answer: "D. None of the above is valid names for variables",
    options: [
      "A. class",
      "B. friend",
      "C. #OnHand",
      "D. None of the above is valid names for variables"
   
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 17,
    question: "You have assigned the address of Value to the pointer P, Which statement will display the value stored in Value?",
    answer: "B. cout<<*Value;",
    options: [
      "A. cout<<P;",
      "B. cout<<*Value;",
      "C. cout<<&P;",
      "D. cout<<*<P;"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 18,
    question: "The void specifier is used if a function does not have return type.",
    answer: "a. True",
    options: [
      "a. True",
      "b. False"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 19,
    question: "You must specify void in parameters if a function does not have any arguments.",
    answer: "a. True",
    options: [
      "a. True",
      "b. False"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 20,
    question: "Type specifier is optional when declaring a function",
    answer: "a. True",
    options: [
      "a. True",
      "b. False"
    ]
  },
];